[{"question": " wait a minute, wait. you\u0092re telling me this actress person is the only woman you ever wanted who didn\u0092t want you back?!", "answer": " yeah! oh my god!  is this what it\u0092s like to be you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " wow, you\u0092re really crazy about her, huh?", "answer": " oh, you have no idea. and-and when we\u0092re on stage i get to-to kiss her and-and touch her, but then she goes home with the director, and it\u0092s like somebody\u0092s ripping out my heart!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh, it\u0092s so great to see you feeling like this!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " monica, uh dad called this morning and ah, aunt silvia passed away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yes!! yes! yeah, yeah, yeah!", "answer": " we were all pretty shaken up about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " wait, am i missing something though? \u0091cause i thought death was something that\u0092s supposed to be sad, in a way.", "answer": " well ah, aunt silvia was, well not a nice person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh, she was a cruel, cranky, old bitch!   and i\u0092m sorry she died. did dad say i get the dollhouse?", "answer": " you get the dollhouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i get the dollhouse!", "answer": " wow, a house for dolls, that is so cool! when i was kid, i had a barrel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " uh, pheebs, you had a barrel for a dollhouse?", "answer": " no, just a barrel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " y'know what, you can play with my dollhouse.", "answer": " really?! really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " any time you want. y'know, when i was younger, all i wanted to do was to play with this dollhouse, but no!! it was to be looked at, but never played with.", "answer": " my grandmother used to say that exact same thing to me. opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hey, sophie!", "answer": " hey, rach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " thanks for lunch, chandler. y'know, you didn\u0092t have to walk me all the way back up here.", "answer": " oh, that\u0092s-that\u0092s okay, no problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " honey um, honey, you do realise that we don\u0092t keep the women\u0092s lingerie here in the office?", "answer": " yes, i realise that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " rachel, i need the versachi invoice.  hello! you don\u0092t work for me.", "answer": "  joanna, this is my friend chandler bing  joanna.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " bing! that\u0092s a great name.", "answer": " thanks, it\u0092s ah, gaelic, for \u0091thy turkey\u0092s done.\u0092 so ah, i\u0092m gonna go, nice, nice meeting you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": " bye, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  so ah, what\u0092s wrong with him?", "answer": " oh, nothing, he\u0092s just goofy like that, i actually, hardly notice it anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " oh no, no-no-no, is he ah, married, or involved with anyone?", "answer": " no!! no! he\u0092s not married, or involved, with anyone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, rachel,  actually, y'know what, forget it.", "answer": " well, i\u0092ll ask him for you, if you want me too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " would you? or, is it just to sad and desperate, and y'know something that sophie would do?", "answer": " uh, uh, uh, i am here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " look at it! ohhh! wallpaper\u0092s a little faded, that\u0092s okay. carpet\u0092s a little loose. hardwood floors!!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " oh! ooh! oh monica! it\u0092s so beautiful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i know!!!", "answer": " so, i\u0092m here, ready to play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i brought a bunch of stuff for the house, so check it out. ha-ha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " what\u0092s this?", "answer": " that\u0092s a dog, every house should have a dog.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " not one that can pee on the roof.", "answer": " well, maybe it\u0092s so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  and is this in case the house sneezes?", "answer": " no, no, that\u0092s the ghost for the attic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " i don\u0092t want a ghost.", "answer": " well, nobody wants a ghost. but you\u0092ve got one, because the house is sitting on an ancient indian burial ground.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " wait a minute, the house was built on radioactive waste, and an ancient indian burial ground? that would never happen.", "answer": " okay, obviously you don\u0092t know much about the u.s. government.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " i need to talk to you!", "answer": " sure, what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh, sorry. i meant chandler.", "answer": " i-i know. well if something comes up...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh, i'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.", "answer": " okay, my boss, joanna, when you left, she started asking questions about you...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh-ho, liked what she saw, huh? dug my action, did she? checkin\u0092 out the chan-chan man!", "answer": "  that was  surreal. okay, what do think? are you interested at all?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yeah, she seemed cool, attractive. i\u0092ll do it.", "answer": " oh thank you, chandler, this is so great, she\u0092s gonna love me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  okay, dinosaur attack!! quick, everybody into the house!! ahh-ahh!  roof! rrroof-roof-roof!", "answer": " okay, phoebe, y'know what? that-that\u0092s it, that\u0092s it, all right? no dinosaurs, no ghosts, no giant dogs, okay? they\u0092re not the right size, they\u0092re not victorian, and they just don\u0092t go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " okay,  fine. come dinosaur, we\u0092re not welcome in the house of no imagination.", "answer": " uh, pheebs, while we\u0092re hovering around the subject. i just have to say dinosaurs, they-they don\u0092t go, rrroof!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " hey, kate!", "answer": " morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " listen, i ah, went to that restaurant that you were talking about last week...", "answer": " hey, lovely! come, talk to me a minute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  and i ate the food, i had the fish, it was good, yeah. it was good, yeah...", "answer": " hi, oh, i\u0092m lauren, kate\u0092s understudy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh, hey! joey tribbiani.", "answer": " i know! i-i\u0092m a big fan of yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  what?!", "answer": " i used to umm, schedule my classes so i could watch dr. drake remoray on days of our lives.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " get out of here, really?!", "answer": " absolutely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " oh but then, they went and dropped you down that elevator shaft.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " they gave me the shaft all right.", "answer": "  oh, you\u0092re so funny. listen, umm, what are you doing after rehearsals? do you want to get a drink, or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " well ahh,  yeah! yeah, sure, a drink sounds great.", "answer": " cool! i-i\u0092ll see you then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " all right, it\u0092s time to act, my talking props.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " look everybody, look at my new dollhouse!!", "answer": " wow!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey, what\u0092s this?!", "answer": " oh, okay, it\u0092s the slide instead of stairs. watch this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " it\u0092s very interesting, phoebe.", "answer": " what\u0092s this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " the licorice room, you can eat all the furniture. and, when guests come over, they can stay on the tootsie roll-away bed.", "answer": " this is the coolest house ever!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " all right!", "answer": " i would!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey, guys, guys, did you see my new, china cabinet?! ross and rachel: uh-huh.", "answer": " watch, watch.  ross and rachel: ooohhhh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " and, and!  ross and rachel: ahhhh!!", "answer": "  hey, my father\u0092s house does that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  o-o-o-okay, how did it go? tell me everything.", "answer": " well, the movie was great, dinner was great, and there\u0092s nothing like a cool, crisp new york evening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " hmm.", "answer": " of course, i didn\u0092t get to enjoy any of that, because joanna\u0092s such a big, dull dud!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " chandler is fantastic!!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh god, we just clicked! y\u0092know how people just click? like he came by to pick me up, and i opened the door, and it was just like, click! did he tell you?", "answer": " oh, i....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh, and he\u0092s got such a good heart! doesn\u0092t he have a good heart?", "answer": " oh, i know...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, i know and he\u0092s soo sweet! listen, he said he was going to call, so put him straight through.", "answer": " isn\u0092t this great?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  that guy\u0092s like a cartoon. what do you see in him anyway?", "answer": " he happens to be brilliant. which is more than i can say for that sweater you\u0092re dating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hey, i\u0092m not interested in her sweater! it\u0092s what\u0092s underneath her sweater that counts. and besides, since ah, since when do you care who i\u0092m going out with?", "answer": " i don\u0092t care. why, do you want me to care?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " do you want me to want you to care?", "answer": " do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " what?", "answer": "  okay, i\u0092m afraid to say this, but let\u0092s pick it up where we left off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " come on baby, don\u0092t go. please? what do you say?", "answer": " i\u0092ve got no reason to stay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe we go on in, in a week.", "answer": " hey, it\u0092s gonna be all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  hey! so since we\u0092re getting off early, do you want to go and paint mugs?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " you know! at the place i told you about last night?", "answer": " oh, yeah, with the mug painting. yeah. i was so listening to that. but ah, y'know what, i think i kinda need to work on my stuff tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " oh, okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " g\u0092night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  ah, are you okay?", "answer": " yeah, i guess. look, what are we gonna do about this scene, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know.", "answer": " well umm, maybe if it had more heat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " how do you mean?", "answer": " well, adrian\u0092s looking for a reason to stay, right? victor can\u0092t just kiss her, he\u0092s gotta, gotta really give her a reason, y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " maybe he could slip her the tongue.", "answer": " or maybe, maybe he could grab her, and, and, and, and lift her up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, and then adrian, she maybe she could wrap her legs around his waist.", "answer": " and then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest, and, and his stomach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " and then, then he could use his teeth, his teeth to undo her dress, and, and, and bite her!", "answer": " and then right, right when the scene ends, he could take her with this raw, animal....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " something like that?", "answer": " yeah, that\u0092s pretty much what i had in mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it\u0092s a little early to be drinkin\u0092.", "answer": " no-no, things ah, finally happened with kate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " ohhhhh!", "answer": " you\u0092re kidding?! that\u0092s great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, it was so amazing. after the  love making...", "answer": " oh my.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  i\u0092m telling ya, joanna\u0092s got it all wrong. okay? all i said was, \u0091this was fun. let\u0092s do it again sometime. i\u0092ll give you a call.\u0092", "answer": " ohh, gee. i wonder why she thinks you\u0092re going to call her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " that\u0092s what you say at the end of a date.", "answer": " you can\u0092t just say, \u0091nice to meet you, good night?\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " to her face? look it\u0092s the end of the date, i\u0092m standing there, i know all she\u0092s waiting for is for me to say \u0091i\u0092ll call her\u0092 and it\u0092s just y'know, comes out. i can\u0092t help it, it\u0092s a compulsion.", "answer": " come on rach, when a guy says he\u0092s going to call, it doesn\u0092t mean he\u0092s going to call. hasn\u0092t it ever happened to you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " well, they always called.", "answer": " hmm, bite me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  did he call?", "answer": " no. sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " why?! why?! he said he\u0092d call. why hasn\u0092t he called?", "answer": " maybe he\u0092s intimated by really smart, strong, successful women.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " sophie, would you please climb out of my butt. why hasn\u0092t he called, rachel? why?", "answer": " okay, okay. umm, well ah, maybe he, maybe he feels awkward because you are my boss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " awkward? why should he feel awkward?", "answer": " well...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " the only person that should feel awkward is you, and you didn\u0092t tell him not to call me, did you?", "answer": " no. i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  call her! call her now!", "answer": " multiple, so many paper cuts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " why hasn\u0092t he called rachel? why? why? i don\u0092t understand. why? he said he\u0092ll call. why? why? chandler i\u0092m telling you she has flipped out, she\u0092s gone crazy!", "answer": "  oh, well give me the phone then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " come on, this isn\u0092t funny. she thinks it\u0092s my fault that you haven\u0092t called her. you have to call her!", "answer": " look, you can\u0092t call somebody after this long just to say, \u0091in case you didn\u0092t notice, i don\u0092t like you!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " well then you\u0092re going to have to take her out again.", "answer": " nooo!! she\u0092s really dull! and she gets this gross mascara goop thing in the corner of her eye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " i don\u0092t care! i don\u0092t care! you are going to have to take her out again and end it, and end it in way that she knows it\u0092s actually ended. and, i don\u0092t care how hard it is for you, do not tell her that you will call her again!", "answer": " all right! fine! but it\u0092s just a lunch date, no more than an hour! and from now on i get my own dates, i don\u0092t want you setting me up with anybody ever again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " that\u0092s fine!", "answer": " that\u0092s just a lot of big talk, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " mon?", "answer": "  i\u0092m in the shower!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " so i ah, talked to lauren, kinda told her how things were with us. did you ah, did you talk to marshall?", "answer": " about what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " y'know, about what happened with us.", "answer": " nooo. and there\u0092s really no reason he should find out, so ah let\u0092s not make a big deal about it, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " what are you talking about? it was a big deal. i mean, come on you can\u0092t tell me last night didn\u0092t mean something to you. i-i was there, you\u0092re not that good an actress.", "answer": " look umm, i, i was, i was just caught up in the moment. that\u0092s all it was. joey, i\u0092m-i\u0092m sorry you feel bad, but haven\u0092t you ever sleep with a women where it meant more to her than it did to you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " nooo.", "answer": "  hi, kate!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hi, lauren.", "answer": " hi, lauren.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " sorry i ah, i scared you in there.", "answer": " oh, that\u0092s okay. by the way, i was just checking the shower massager.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  i tried to reach you at work. there\u0092s....been a fire.", "answer": " what?! oh my...  oh my god!! what happened?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " well, we believe it originated here.  in the aroma room.", "answer": " all right. did everyone get out okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " well, the giraffe\u0092s okay. and so is the pirate.", "answer": " ohh. what is this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " no phoebe, don\u0092t look! you don\u0092t want to see what\u0092s under there!!", "answer": "  ohh, the-the foster puppets!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " it\u0092s not a big deal. it\u0092s, just it\u0092s right here,  and it\u0092s all the time.", "answer": " well, thanks again for lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " it was, wasn\u0092t it?", "answer": " the food there was, was great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " wasn\u0092t it?", "answer": " so take care.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " you too.", "answer": " well, this was great. i\u0092ll give you a call. we should do it again sometime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " great! i\u0092m looking forward to it. rachel, any messages?", "answer": " sophie\u0092s desk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  chandler!! are you gonna call her!", "answer": " noo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " chandler!!", "answer": " look, i\u0092m sorry. okay? i\u0092m weak, and pathetic, and sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " ahhhh--i\u0092m not going to call you.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry. i\u0092m-i\u0092m-i\u0092m sorry that i said i was going to when i\u0092m not. look, this has nothing to do with you, y'know? and this isn\u0092t rachel\u0092s fault. it\u0092s me. i have serious, serious problems when it comes to women. i have issues with commitment, intimacy,  mascara goop. and i\u0092m really sorry, it\u0092s just that this is not, this isn\u0092t going to work out.", "answer": " well, this isn\u0092t how i was hoping how this would end, but i guess i have to appreciate your honesty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " yeah, o-okay.", "answer": " so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}]